剧情回顾...
Previously on Lost...
Boone  你看到什么?
Boone, what do you see?
好了  都起来
All right, all of you, get up.
我们准备出发了
We're moving out.
出发去哪?
Moving out where?
回到你原来的地方
Back to where you came from.
你的同伴独自跑到丛林里了
Your buddy ran off into the jungle.
Michael  他离开了
Michael, he just left.
Walt!
那我们该如何?  等他?
What are we supposed to do? Wait for him?
你要干什么?
What are you doing?
帮他寻找他的朋友
I'm going to help him find his friend.
声明: 本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
欢迎访问官方论坛  www.YYeTs.net 在线观看 剧情讨论 学习交流
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：Singa校对：雯雯  七色九天
后期：xyz 双语制作：啊多
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
你很渴吗  狗?
You thirsty, dog?
你总是很渴  对吗?
Yeah, you're always thirsty, aren't you?
那就喝
So, drink.
来
Come on.
收拾好你东西
Gather your things.
我们去哪?
Where are we going?
Sayid?
来  在这边
Right over here.
我们去哪?
Where are we going?
觉得如何?
What do you think?
里面有东西吗?
Does it have an inside?
你什么时候做这些的?
When did you do this?
全属于你
It's all yours.
谢谢
Thank you.
不用谢
You are quite welcome.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你要一直都带着枪?
You need to carry that all the time?
我带着  是因为有人需要保护
I only carry it because I have someone to protect.
Ana  休息超过1小时了
Ana, it's gotta be over an hour.
是否应该赶路了呢?
Shouldn't we start moving again?
再呆一会
Let them rest a little while longer.
但万一"他们"来呢?
Yeah, but what if they come?
她迷路了
She's lost.
我没迷路
I am not lost.
那你告诉我 Ponce de León(西班牙冒险家) 我们该走哪条路呢?
Then tell me, Ponce de León, which way are we supposed to go?
那好  天才  你要走哪条路?
All right then, genius, which way would you go?
我只是跟着你
I'm with you.
坐在一旁  等Eko先生来给我们带路
Sit tight and wait for Mr Eko to show up and guide us.
如果你朋友不是擅自跑了
If your friend didn't run off
Eko会在这  不是吗?
Eko would still be here now, wouldn't he?
你却抛下你朋友不管
You sure didn't have any problem leaving him behind, though, huh?
Mike只关心他和他儿子
Mike only cares about himself and his kid.
况且关我什么事!
Neither's got squat to do with me.
很高兴你这么想
Glad you feel that way.
还以为见不着你了
Didn't expect to see you again.
好了  英雄  我知道 我的手臂要断了
Yeah, yeah, Chewie, I know. My arm's about to fall off.
-你还好吧?    -很好
-You OK?     -Yes.
但我们要起程了
But we have to go.
我见到"他们"了
I saw them.
-什么?  -你见到"他们"?  -有多少人?
-What?  -What your means saw?  -How many were there?
-有见到孩子吗?    -Libby
-Did you see the kids?    -Libby.
我们得走了  马上
We need to go. Now.
好的
All right
我们出发
we're moving out.
快
Now.
那么说  这些...
So, does all this...
帐篷  花...
the tent, the flowers...
意味着我们是认真的?
mean that we're serious now?
当然不是
Quite definitely not.
在荒岛上每遇到一个女孩 我都会为她这么做
I do this for all the girls I meet on deserted islands.
别走开
Don't go anywhere.
-你要去哪?  -去拿点水
-Where are you going?  -To get some water.
让我来
Let me.
我很快回来
I'll be right back.
真快
That was quick.
迷 失
第二季 第六集
没见到什么
There's nothing.
那边没人
There's no one there.
告诉你我见到Walt了
I'm telling you. I saw Walt.
-只是个梦  Shannon   -Walt当时就在这
-It was a dream, Shannon    -He was here.
我真的见到他 他跑进了帐篷
I saw him. He went into the tent.
我只是出去一小会 你肯定是睡着了
I was only gone a few moments. You must have fallen asleep...
这不是梦!
This was not a dream.
-我见到Walt   -那现在他在哪呢?
-I saw Walt!  -Then where is he?
怎么回事?
What's going on?
没什么  梦而已  没什么事
Nothing. It's just a dream. Everything's fine.
Shannon...
怎么了?
What's wrong?
Shannon做恶梦了
Shannon had a nightmare.
怎么他醒了?
And why is he up?
-我弄醒他的   -你弄醒他?
-I woke him.    -You woke him?
我听到尖叫声  我担心
I heard screams, I got worried.
你想我让他一个在那边?
Would you rather I had left him alone?
你听到尖叫声  那你就弄醒孩子 然后来看?
You woke up the baby and ran towards them?
我想她需要帮忙
It sounded like she needed help...
他需要喂食了
He's gonna need feeding.
看来他明天一整天 都要睡不着和烦躁不安了
He's going to be up all night and fussy all day.
-你说什么?    -没什么
-Sorry.    -All right.
来 给我抱抱
No harm done.Give him here, then. I got him...
乖
It's OK.
等等
Wait.
回来  我们好好谈谈
Come back and let's talk about this.
你相信我吗?
Do you believe me?
我见到什么  我心中有数
No. I know what I saw.
很美  Sophie
Beautiful, Sophie.
能把肩膀放低一点吗?
OK, can you bring your shoulders down for me a little?
站直  好  完毕
Extend up. Good. And, finish.
很好  姑娘们
Very nice, ladies.
我爸爸见到我跳吗?
Did my papa see me?
应该见到
I think so.
很好  这堂课你们表现很好  姑娘们
Wonderful. All right, thank you for a great class today, ladies.
跳得不错  Gina
Very nice work, Gina.
他要我来做他家保姆  你信吗?
He wants me to be his au pair. Can you believe that?
保姆  我的天
Au pair, my ass.
"在我的大房子里照顾我的孩子"
"Live in my big house, take care of my kids. "
然后你知道的  很..
Next thing, it's..
"噢  很抱歉 我不知道你在洗澡"
"Oh, I am sorry. I did not know you were in the shower. "
噢...真变态
Please. What a perv.
喂?
Hello?
Shannon  你父亲出了事
Shannon, your father's been in an accident.
我正赶去Sebastian家  那边见
I'm on my way to St Sebastian's... I'll meet you there.
-Rutherford夫人?     -嗯?
-Mrs Rutherford?     -Yes?
谈一下好吗?
Why don't we talk down here?
医生  我丈夫Adam... 他怎么样了?
Doctor, my husband, Adam. How is he?
你丈夫的车和一山地跑车正面撞在一起
Your husband was in a head-on collision with an SUV.
他内脏严重受伤
He suffered massive internal injuries.
在事故现场  当时已停止呼吸
He stopped breathing at the site of the accident.
恐怕我们无法救活他了
I'm afraid we were unable to resuscitate him.
很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
-我能去看看他吗?     -当然可以
-May I see him?     -Of course.
你女儿要不要来?
Would your daughter like to come?
继女
Stepdaughter.
来  Shannon
Come on, Shannon.
离他们营地还有多远?
How much further to their camp?
还要一天  可能不止
A day. Maybe more.
可能不用一天
Maybe less.
谢谢说得这么精确
Thanks for being so specific.
该死的!
Damn it!
我没事 我很好
I'm OK. I'm fine.
让我来看看你的肩膀?
You wanna let me just take a look at your shoulder?
-你是医生?  -临床心理学家
-What are you, a doctor?  -Clinical psychologist.
你是精神病医生吧?
You're a shrink.
也许你该和我肩膀聊聊
Maybe you ought to talk to my shoulder.
你是怎么受伤的?
How'd you get shot anyway?
当时我拿着枪
With a gun.
在他们抢走我孩子时受的伤
He got shot when they took my kid.
很糟糕  对吗?
It's bad, right?
对  挺糟糕的
Yeah, it's bad.
但不会有很大问题
But it's not real bad.
走吧  没事的
Come on, you're gonna be OK.
走吧
Let's go.
我没事
I'm all right. I'm fine.
我来帮你好吗?
Let me give you a hand, OK?
舱内有干衣机  为什么还要晾衣服?
tell me again why we're doing this here when there's a dryer in the hatch?
我不喜欢那舱
I don't like the hatch.
因为那个"世界末日"按钮?
It's because of the doomsday button, isn't it?
有阳光  有新鲜空气 谁还要干衣机?
Well, who needs a dryer when we've got sun and fresh air?
不要宠坏自己了  对吗?
Wouldn't wanna spoil ourselves, now, would we?
嗯  "宠坏"
Yeah, "spoil".
你们知道Michael和Walt
Do you know where Michael and Walt
把他们没带上船的东西放在哪吗?
left the stuff that they didn't take with them on the raft?
-什么东西?     -衣物
-What kind of stuff?     -Their clothes?
我想还在沙滩上
I think their stuff's still on the beach
在他们帐篷的后面
back where their tent is.
谢谢
Thanks.
真可怜
Poor thing.
在岛上失去心爱的人 那滋味真不好受
Can't be easy, losing the one person you love on the island.
来  闻一下  这是他的  对吗?
Here, smell this. That's his, right?
来  好好闻一下
Come on, get a good whiff.
你总是独自跑掉去找他?
You're always trying to run off and find him
那就去找他  找Walt
then find him. Find Walt.
好狗  找Walt
Good dog. Find Walt!
我知道我叫醒了你  对不起  真对不起
I know I woke you and I'm so very, very sorry,
但怎么8个钟头了  还没睡着呢?
but, please, staying awake for eight hours straight?
这惩罚太残忍  太重了吧?
Isn't that cruel and unusual punishment?
摇篮怎么了?
How's that cradle treating you?
摇篮很好  问题出在孩子上
The cradle's great, it's the baby that's the problem.
-怎么了?     -他就是不睡
-What's wrong?     -He just won't sleep.
我来试试?
May I?
好
Sure.
婴儿喜欢被裹起来的感觉
Babies like the feeling of being constricted.
到长大了  才不想被"裹"起来
It's not until we're older that we develop the desire to be free.
给
There.
我想每个人都比我了解我孩子
You know, I think everybody knows more about my baby than me.
每个人?
Everybody?
Charlie昨晚告诫我 弄醒他会让他烦躁不安
Charlie read me the riot act last night for waking him.
看现在这情形  看来他说得对
And as mad as it made me, turns out he was right.
我们就像这孩子的母亲和父亲
It's like we're playing "Mum and Dad" to this baby
然而我却不记得我嫁过他
yet I don't remember marrying him.
我说真的  实际上我们是陌生人
Seriously. We're practically strangers.
就我所知而言 Charlie可能是某个宗教怪胎
For all I know, Charlie could be some religious freak.
我很怀疑那一点
I seriously doubt that.
那他为什么到处拿着一个圣母像?
Then why does he carry around a Virgin Mary statue?
什么?
A what?
一个小雕像
You know, one of the little statues?
他说在丛林里面找到的
He says he found it in the jungle.
难道是那东西?
How about that?
-亲人逝去总令人悲痛不已  不是吗?   -Boone!
-Death sucks, doesn't it?  -Boone!
我感到很难过  Shan
I'm so sorry, Shan.
你总算回来了
You came back.
Marky Mark海报哪里去了?
Where'd the poster of Marky Mark go?
我18岁了  Boone
I'm 18, Boone.
你妈妈会很生气的
Your mom's gonna freak.
这是一种振作
It's a wake.
说真的  要振作  谁不喝点酒呢?
I mean, seriously, who doesn't serve booze at a wake?
苏格兰酒
Scotch
敬你的父亲
To your dad.
也许打这后  你来纽约找我?
Maybe after all this you'll come visit me in New York.
我不必去找你
I won't have to visit
如果我得到在Martha Graham舞蹈公司的工作
if I get that job at the Martha Graham Dance Company.
我会在那住
I'll be living there.
对  实习
Right. Internship.
我知道只有三千分之一的机会
I know it's, like, a one in three thousand chance, but
但我也许能行
I might get it.
绝对可以
Absolutely.
你和我妈妈谈过吗?
Have you spoken to my mother?
我们互不理睬的 独自尝着自己的苦水
She's going through her thing and I'm going through mine.
你们有相处过吗?
Have you two been getting along?
她讨厌我
She hates me.
试试和她聊聊
Just try to talk to her.
从他们结婚的第一天起 她就不满我和他的关系...
From day one, she resented my relationship with him.
我和爸爸的关系
With Dad.
我们要休息一下
We need a break.
五分钟
Five minutes.
给
Here.
你看什么?
What are you looking at?
我们要往岛内走
We have to cut inland.
什么? 进入丛林?
What? Into the jungle?
他们说他们的人在海边 如果我们继续走...
They said their people were on the beach. If we keep walking...
这海岸弯成一个半岛
The beach curves into a peninsula.
可能走不过去
It may not be passable.
可能走不过?
May not?
对
May not.
你这么做是想把这家伙快点送回去  对吗?
You're doing this to get the cowboy back faster, aren't you?
你拿我们的生命冒险 来帮他?
You would risk our lives to help him?
这是唯一的方法
It's the only way I know.
我更喜欢不说话时的你
I liked you better when you weren't talking.
真不敢相信他还在睡
I can't believe he's still asleep.
婴儿总爱在襁褓中入睡
Swaddling works every time.
你想抱一下吗?
Hey, do you want to hold him?
不用了
That's OK.
伸手出来
Put your arms out.
没关系的
It's OK.
来
There.
-他气息很好  -很好闻是不是?
-He smells good.   -He does, doesn't he?
那当然
Yeah.
-你好  Charlie  -你好
-Hello, Charlie.  -Hello.
John刚教我一招  用襁褓包
Hey, John just taught me a new trick. Swaddling.
这法子很好
That's excellent.
我过来照顾他 以便你可以散下步
I just came to take him so you could have your walk.
你来得正是时候 我要起程了
Well, great timing. Yeah, I got to get going.
抱着了
I got him.
谢谢你的帮忙  John
Well, thanks for your help, John.
不客气
You're welcome.
什么?
What?
我没事  我没事  该死
I'm fine. I'm fine, damn it.
别出声!
Shut up!
什么? 话都不能说?
What? They can't talk at all?
如果给"他们"听到 大家都没命的
If he talks he'll get us all killed.
什么东西?  "他们"?
By what? Them?
我想他们住在沿这路 要一天路程的那边
I thought they lived a day back that way.
你还是住口  叫你的同伴上路吧
How about you shut your mouth and get your buddy over here moving.
你们到底怎么了?
What happened to you people?
你想我们带你回去?  好
You want us to take you back with us? fine.
但如果你想让我保持安静
But you want me to keep quiet
那你要告诉我  为什么我要这么做
Then you need to tell me why I have to.
我们来这里的第一晚 他们就来了
They came the first night that we got here.
他们抓走我们三个人
They took three of us.
然后两周之内都没什么事发生
Nothing happened for two weeks.
但两周后  他们又来  再抓走九个
Then they came back, and took nine more.
他们很聪明
They're smart.
他们是禽兽
And they're animals.
随时随地他们都可能出现
And they could be anywhere, at any time.
现在我们穿越丛林...
Now we're moving through the jungle...
这个属于他们的丛林...
their jungle...
只有这样  才救得了你这个乡下人朋友
just so that you can save your little hick friend over here.
如果你幻想一把枪一发子弹能制服他们
And if you think that one gun and one bullet is gonna stop them
那你就慢慢幻想
think again.
闭上你的臭嘴  继续上路
So, shut your mouth, and keep moving.
他们抢走了我儿子
They took my son.
他们抢走很多东西
They took a lot of things.
我明白你失去亲人的感受
I know what it is to lose someone you care deeply about.
你真的认为我全因Boone才这样?
You really think that this is all about Boone?
我见到Walt  Sayid
I saw Walt, Sayid.
那为什么我们会坐在Boone的坟边?
Then why are we sitting at Boone's grave?
-你回去  Sayid  -你去哪里?
-Just go back, Sayid.  -Where are you going?
在找Walt
To find him.
信来了
It came.
真的?
What?
-天啊  -打开看看
-Oh, my God.  -Open it.
-我不行  -什么?
-I can't open it.  -You what?
你来打开
You open it.
你等这信等了六周 没理由让我来打开
You've been waiting 6 months for this letter. No way I'm opening it.
我成了!
I got it!
-你成了?  -成了!
-You got it?  -I got it!
噢  天啊  你要到纽约去了!
Oh, my God, you're going to New York!
天啊
Oh, my God!
喂?
Hello?
对  我就是
Yeah, this is her.
那不可能
That's impossible.
好的  你确定?
OK, are you sure?
当然
Of course.
我会的
I will certainly do that.
对不起
Sorry.
什么?
What?
我房租卡没钱了
My rent cheque bounced.
但你看起来...很有钱
But you're like... rich.
对不起  我应该给点东西你喝的
I would have offered you a drink
但十分钟后我要参加一个会议
but I have a meeting in ten minutes.
我的房租卡没钱了
Yeah. My cheques are bouncing.
那是因为你要搬出去住
That happens when you withdraw
而你又不存款  Shannon
and you don't deposit. Shannon
什么时候我可以拿到爸爸留给我的钱?
When do I get the money Dad left me?
来自遗嘱的钱
The money from the will.
没有什么遗嘱
There was no will.
什么?
What?
Shannon  你父亲和我有个生前信托
Shannon, your father and I had a living trust.
所有东西都归我
Everything passed to me.
恐怕没有东西指定给你的
I'm afraid there was nothing specifically designated for you.
他为什么要那么做?
Why would he do that?
也许他想你自力更生
Well, maybe he just wanted you to find your own way.
我们都要工作  Shannon
We all have to work, Shannon.
工作才有钱
And most of us are the better for it.
我会工作  我刚得到这个有名的实习机会
I can work. I just got this really prestigious internship
我暂时不会赚到钱
and I'm not gonna make any money for a while
但我将会工作...每天16个小时
but I'm gonna be working like 16 hours a day.
我知道你唯一能连续做16个小时的事 就是睡觉
The only thing I've ever seen you do 16 hours a day straight is sleep.
我只是要到纽约去
I just need to get to New York.
我只是需要点资金起步
I need just something to get started.
我会还你的
I'll pay you back.
这周是实习
This week it's an internship.
去年是什么来着 内景设计?
Last year it was, what... interior design?
你永远还不了钱给我
You'll never pay me back.
那样你只会更憎恨自己
And you'll only hate yourself even more.
我真的很需要钱  Sabrina
I really want this, Sabrina.
我会做得很出色的
I can do this.
对不起  Shannon
I'm sorry, Shannon.
你自己看着办吧
You're on your own.
双六  你真厉害
Double sixes, how nice for you.
运气
Lucky.
希望你不要想歪了
I hope you didn't get the wrong idea
看到我抱着孩子
about seeing me with the baby.
什么想歪了?
What wrong idea would that be?
你和Claire感情很好
You and Claire are close
你花很多时间来陪Aaron
and you spend a lot of time with Aaron.
我只是不想我越过我的底线
I just wouldn't want to overstep my bounds.
她有没有告诉你我们发生口角?
Did she tell you we had a fight?
她认为这不是口角
She didn't say it was a fight.
她打算忘了这件事
She was gonna give it up, you know...
为了孩子
for adoption.
她告诉你了吗?
She told you that?
在我做摇篮的时候她告诉了我
Yeah. When I built the cradle.
那也是
Oh, of course.
在你做摇篮时
Yeah. When you built the cradle.
-为什么问这个?    -她...
-Why do you ask?    -She...
做为妈妈  她还有很多东西要学
She's got a bit to learn... about being a mum.
责任  还有很多很多
Responsibility and all.
嗯  有件有趣的事情要说说
Now, that's an interesting thing to say
海洛因瘾君子
for a heroin addict.
正在戒毒的瘾君子
Recovering addict.
正在戒毒
Recovering.
该你掷了
It's your turn.
来  我来帮你
Here, let me help you.
我来
I got it.
我说我来  伙计 休息一下
I said I got him, man. Take a break.
听着...
Listen...
什么? 你突然关心起我来了?
What? You suddenly give a damn about me?
你们两个都不要理我
Just leave me alone. Both of you.
我行
I got it.
来
Come here
Come on.
嘿  Sawyer  没事吧?
Hey, Sawyer. Hey, you OK?
我丢下你不理...
I would have left you behind.
住口  伙计  不要试图...
Shut up, man. Don't try to...
我确实曾抛下你不理
I did leave you behind.
好在我不是你
Yeah, well, good thing I aren't you.
不要  Sawyer!
No, Sawyer.
Sawyer!
水! 水!
Water! Water!
Sawyer!
Sawyer! 醒醒  老友
Sawyer! Sawyer. Come on, man.
给
Here you go.
快
Here.
Sawyer
他到底怎么了?
What's the matter with him?
他发烧了 伤口感染  身体脱水
The fever. He's got an infection, dehydrated.
我们得继续前进
We gotta keep moving.
-什么?     -得继续前进
-What?     -We gotta keep going.
你想原地不动  好 但我们要动身了
You wanna stay? That's fine, but we're rolling out.
我们不能丢下他不理  Ana
We can't just leave him, Ana.
也许如果我们再休息一会 他会恢复意识
Maybe if we rest a while, he'll regain consciousness.
休息? 在这?
Rest? Here?
你还记得我们所发生的事 他们怎样对我们吗?
Do you remember what happened to us? What they did to us?
你还记得Goodwin吗?
Do you remember Goodwin?
Ana说得对  也许我们要上路了
Ana's right, maybe we should just push on.
我不知道什么Goodwin
I don't remember Goodwin,
对他的事我感到很抱歉 但我可不管
and I'm really sorry about whatever happened to him, but I don't care.
Eko先生?
Mr Eko,
能帮我做个担架吗?
can you help me make a stretcher?
Bernard  我需要4根木棒 5英尺长  结实的那种
Bernard, I need four sticks... sturdy ones, about five feet long.
好  知道了
Got it.
你打算抬你朋友走?
You're gonna carry your friend.
对  我们打算抬他
Yeah. We're gonna carry him.
为什么你这么做  Shannon?
Why are you doing this, Shannon?
我没叫你跟我来
I didn't ask you to follow me.
你这样子出来  很容易迷路和受伤的
You'd rather be alone and get lost or hurt.
我不需要你的帮忙  Sayid
I don't need your help, Sayid!
Walt不在这里
Walt is not out here!
你跟着的是条拉布拉多狗 不是警犬
You are following a Labrador not police dog.
找在海洋中一只木筏上的小孩
to find a boy who is on a raft...
-他不在木筏上     -你说什么?
-He's not on the raft.    -What are you talking about?
我们在沙滩上找到那瓶子
We found the bottle on the beach.
那个他们带在筏上的装有纸条的瓶子?
The bottle with the messages that they brought with them?
我知道他在这里某个地方
I know he's out here somewhere.
我见到Walt!
I saw Walt.
木筏没有了  他孤身一人
And the raft is gone and he is all alone.
Shannon...
用力
Come on!
Cindy!
好了
什么? 她刚才就在这里...
What? She was just here...
Cindy
Cindy在哪里了?
Where's Cindy?
刚才还在这里的
What? She was just here...
Cindy  Cindy!
-我不知道  她...    -他们捉了她去?
-I don't know, she...    -Did they take her?
她怎么一下子不见了?
How could she just be gone?
Cindy  Cindy!
我去找她
I'm going after her.
不  我们在一起
No. We stay together.
我们分开  那正合他们的意
We split up, we give them what they want.
全是你的错
This is all your fault!
我们本不应穿越丛林的
We never should have gone through the jungle.
你用我们的性命冒险去救他 而他已经快死了
You risked our lives to save him. He's already dead.
这次错在你
This one's on you.
那什么鬼东西?
What the hell is that?
天啊
Oh, God.
跑!
Run!
她不答应
She said no.
我想她知道我为什么要向她要钱
I guess she knew why I asked for the money.
在纽约  我可以到你那里短期借宿吗
Can I crash at your place in New York for just a little while?
直到我站稳脚跟
Until I get on my feet.
我要离开纽约 她给了我一份工作
I'm leaving New York. She offered me a job.
你要为你妈妈干活?
You're going to work for your mother?
那份工作真的很好  Shannon
It's a really good job, Shannon.
现在我仅有这么多
This is all I have
这个月尾我的信托基金就会入我帐户
but my trust fund will kick in at the end of the month.
那样的话  我绝对可以养活你
And after that I can absolutely keep you afloat.
谢谢  但是...
Thank you, but...
我得想个法子自己赚钱
I'm gonna figure out a way to make my own money.
但谁知道以后会怎样 拿去吧!
But who knows when that's gonna be?  Just take it
你认为我做不到?
What, you don't think I can do it?
我没这么说
I didn't say that.
你信我还是不信我  Boone?
Do you believe I can or don't you, Boone?
好  你知道吗
OK, you know what?
我只想你拿回你的钱 给你妈妈卖命去
I really want you to just take your money. Go work for your mother.
我不想要
I don't want your money!
-我只是想帮你  Shannon!  -我不想要你的钱!
-I'm trying to help you, Shannon!  -I don't want your money!
那好
OK.
Shannon!
你没事吧
Are you OK?
不要帮我!
Do not help me up!
我们回去吧
Let's go back.
为什么你不信我?
Why don't you believe me?
我需要你相信我
I need you to believe in me!
-我真的相信你  -你没有!
-I do believe in you.  -You don't.
没人信我
No one does.
他们认为我只是个笑话
They think that I am some kind of joke.
他们认为我很没用
They think I'm worthless.
Shannon  你并非没用
Shannon, you are not worthless.
你现在是这么说...
You say that now...
但你还是不信我...
but you don't...
你将抛下我不理...
You're just gonna leave me.
我知道我们一旦离开这里 你就会抛下我
I know, as soon as we get out of here, you're just gonna leave me.
我永远不会抛下你
I will never leave you.
我爱你
I love you.
我也相信你
And I believe you.
真的吗?
You do?
真的
I do.
你见到他了吗?
Do you see him?
Walt!
Walt!  -Shannon!
Walt...等等...
Walt, wait...
Shannon!
==============|  YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====